Sparks Photographs
undated
- Photographs, 1860-1997
  - Fraternity brothers of Charles Sparks, 1900-1910; UNRS-P2017-13_860; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of five young men sitting outside a building labeled 704. They are all wearing suits and hats. No identification. Possibly members of the same fraternity to which Charles Meigs Sparks belonged.
  - Charles Sparks with some fraternity brothers, 1900-1910; UNRS-P2017-13_861; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of five young men outside a building labeled 704. They are all wearing suits and hats. Two men are sitting while the other three are standing. The man standing on the left is possible Charles Meigs Sparks. Possibly a group photo of Charles with some fraternity brothers.
  - Two men outside a warehouse, 1900-1910; UNRS-P2017-13_862; Postcard; 3 3/8 x 5 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of two young men sitting outside of a building. One is wearing a hat, thumbing his nose, and has an arm around the other man's shoulder. No identification. Possibly members of the same fraternity to which Charles Meigs Sparks belonged.
  - Unidentified man, 1900-1910; UNRS-P2017-13_863; Postcard; 3 3/8 x 5 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a portrait of a young man in a suit and holding a hat. Pressed into the corner: Hansen's Studio 1639 Fillmore St. San Francisco. No identification. Possibly a member of the same fraternity to which Charles Meigs Sparks belonged.
  - Christmas Greetings from Lydia MacKenzie, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_864; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 7 1/2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photograph of a silhouetted woman in profile, possibly Lydia Mackenzie. She is wearing a hat. Caption on front: When I was young I used to say - A very merry Christmas day! My Style has changed and now I say - God bless you all on Christmas day! Lydia Mackenzie.
    Possibly a relative of James MacKenzie, the husband of Maud Sparks MacKenzie.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_865; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard depicting a winter river scene in a small oval. There is a boarder of white flowers. Caption on front: May the New Year be a Happy one for You And happy to those whose happiness depends on Yours.
    There are two copies of this postcard.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_866; Postcard; 3 1/2 x 5 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a winter river scene with a house and barn by the river. The scene is enclosed in a circle at the bottom of the card. The edges are silver with a bordering mimicing the motif of aged parchment. Caption on front: Hearty New Year Wishes.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_867; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard with a New Year greeting. On the left is an oval depicting a winter scene. In the scene is a small house, a woman carrying buckets, and two cows by a river. The border of white flowers. Caption on front: I Greet You in Friendship's Name - I know no deeper, better way to say that I wish You A Happy New Year.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_868; Postcard; 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard depicting a small man wearing a wig, three cornered hat, and a purple jacket stepping out of a grandfather clock. Caption on front: I wish you a Happy New Year! I pray its course may bring A calm content-ment to your heart Life's richest offering May griefs be few, may friends be true: May hopes burst into flower, May vanished rares and an-swered prayers Lighten each passing hour.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_869; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a winter scene on the left with a New Year's greeting on the right. In an oval, the winter scene shows a woman walking along a snow covered hill with a house in the background. The border is made up of white flowers. Caption on front: I send a Loving Thought to Greet You this New Year - May each day of it be brighter and more perfect than the last.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_870; Postcard; 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year's greeting. Behind the greeting are flowers and rays of sunshine. Caption on front: A Happy New Year to you Days of Shadow, days of Sun, Come and go for everyone; Dear one I would wish for thee Many Sunny years to see.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_871; Postcard; 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year greeting. The border consistes of a birch/aspen bark design. There is a beam at the top with pink flowers surrounding it and at the bottom is a small winter scene of a church and a couple crossing a bridge over a river. Caption on front: A Happy New Year.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_872; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year greeting. The greeting is on a background of parchment surrounded by a night winter scene. Caption on front: A Happy New Year with nothing to distress you - Every-thing to bless you.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_873; Postcard; 3 1/4 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year greeting. Above the greeting is a castle on a snowy mountainside. The border consists of wavy stripes and roses. Caption on front: A Happy New Year May Good Fortune follow you and Adversity shun you the whole year through.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_874; Postcard; 3 1/4 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year greeting. Above the greeting is a tree with decorations and some hanging garlands. The greeting is surrounded by a green striped border with holly. Caption on front: Another New Year and the same old sincere greeting Happy New Year.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_875; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year greeting. The greeting is on a background of parchment surrounded by a night winter scene. Caption on front: Happy New Year! Many Happy New Years! Each one happier than the last.
  - New Year Greeting, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_876; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a New Year greeting. The greeting is on a background of parchment surrounded by a night winter scene. Caption on front: May all good things pursue you! This is my New Year Greeting to you.
  - Train at Spokane Terminal, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_877; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a group of people standing in a city street and boarding a trolley train. Caption on front: All aboard for the Lakes! Caption on verso: For delightful lake and river outings take the Coeur d'Alene electric trains at Spokane Terminal, Main and Lincoln Sts., Spokane. Liberty Lake, Hayden Lake, Coeur d'Alene Lake and beautiful shadowy St. Joe River all afford ideal places for picnics, summer camps or daily excursions.
  - Summer homes at Del Cardo Bay, Lake Coeur d’Alene, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_878; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a beach with coniferous trees at the edge and some cabins near the trees. Caption on front: Summer homes at Del Cardo Bay, Lake Coeur d'Alene. Caption on verso: Cozy cottages on the lake shores about Spokane are inexpensive and make delightful summer homes. Special commutation rates via Coeur d'Alene electric line.
  - At the Coeur d’Alene Boat Club Regatta, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_879; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a rowing team in striped red and white shirts on a lake. There are other boats on the water around them. Caption on front: At the Coeur d'Alene Boat Club Regatta. Caption on verso: Boating parties afford delightful outings on Lake Coeur d'Alene. For particulars regarding launches, address Waldo G. Paine, G.P.A., Electric Terminal, Spokane. Tel. Ex. 22.
  - Entrance to the Hotel Idaho, Coeur d’Alene, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_880; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of the entrance to a large three story building. There is a patio on the second floor with several figures dressed in white standing on it. Caption on front: Entrance to Hotel Idaho, Coeur d'Alene. Caption on verso: Located on the lake front, nearby electric railway and steamer terminals, Hotel Idaho is convenient for tourists, and an objective point for trolley, automobile and coaching parties, J. E. O'Brien, Mgr., Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
  - Beautiful Shadowy St. Joe River, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_881; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of the St. Joe River. The shores of the river are lined with trees. Caption on front: Beautiful Shadowy St. Joe River. Caption on verso: The St. Joe River is navigable a distance of 40 miles from Lake Coeur d'Alene to St. Joe. For perfect reflections and shadow scenery this river is unsurpassed. Daily excursions to St. Joe River via C. d'A. & S. electric line and Red Collar steamers.
  - Camping at the St. Joe River, Idaho, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_882; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of some people at a campsite on the edge of the St. Joe river. There are three people in two rowboats on the water. Caption on front: Camping on the St. Joe River, Idaho. Caption on verso: Coll nights, no mosquitoes and excellent trout, bass and perch fishing make summer camping on St. Joe River ideal. Double daily steamer service via Red Collar S. S. Line from Coeur d'Alene city. For camp locations address J. C. White, Mgr. Red Collar S. S. Line, Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
  - “Palousers” camping on the St. Joe River, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_883; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a group of people camping in a forest meadow. There are three pitched tents, and five people gathered around a picnic table. Caption on front: Wont you stay to breakfast? "Palousers" Camping on the St. Joe River. Caption on verso: Ideal locations for summer camps are found on the banks of the shadowy St. Joe River. Double daily steamer service to and from Coeur d'Alene connecting with electric line for Spokane. For camp locations, address J. C. White, Mgr., Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
  - Steamer Idaho leaving St. Joe, Idaho, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_884; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a steamboat on a river. There is a rowboat in the foreground. Caption on the front: Steamer Idaho leaving St. Joe, Idaho. Caption on the verso: During the summer months round trips from Spokane to head of navigation on the St. Joe River are run by the Coeur d'Alene Electric Railway and the Red Collar S. S. Line. The trip by rail and water is 200 miles and affords magnificant scenery.
  - St. Petersburg, Fla. Residence Hon. Joseph C. Sibley, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_885; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of several buildings. The one on the right has an American flag out front, the one in the middle has a belltower behind it, and the third has a two story porch. Caption on front: St. Petersburg, Fla. Residence Hon. Joseph C. Sibley.
  - In a Florida Orange Grove, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_886; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of two orange pickers in an orange grove. One is standing by crates of oranges and the other is at the top of a ladder. Caption on front: In a Florida Orange Grove.
  - Women’s building – Southwestern University, Georgetown, Tex., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_887; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a three story brick building with a large field in front of it. Caption on front: Women's building - Southwestern University, Georgetown, Tex.
  - Cody Memorial Library, Southwestern University, Georgetown, Tex., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_888; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a three story building with several trees in front of it. Caption on front: Cody Memorial Library - Southwestern University Georgetown, Tex.
  - Georgetown High School, Georgetown, Tex., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_889; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a large two story brick building with a bush in front. There is a sidewalk leading to the entrance of the building. Caption on front: Georgetown High School Georgetown, Tex.
  - U.S. Post Office, Georgetown, Tex., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_890; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a tall brick building with an ornate lintel over the main entrance. Caption on front: U.S. Post Office Georgetown, Tex.
  - Highway Bridge, Georgetown, Tex., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_891; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a large road. There are some trees in the distance on either side of the road. Caption on front: Highway Bridge Georgetown, Tex.
    There are two copies of this postcard. Copy 2 - Handwritten on verso in pencil: Benton please save this card it is a photo of my fathers old home. Urrand(?) Mother. Handwritten on verso in ink: This is looking across the two bridges crossing the north south Gabriel rivers. Grandpa's place on left between the rivers.
  - Williamson County Court House, Georgetown, Tex., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_892; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a three story building with a rotunda on top. Caption on front: Williamson County Court House Georgetown, Tex.
    There are two copies of this postcard. Copy 2 - Handwritten on verso: B 3112 Windsor Rd./Horrison Wilson Co. Dial 2-9841/ 22 floro Eisell halt bldg /x H Brushes Co. Corner of Colorado & 7th street/ Preston and Dyke/305 W 11th St. Dial 8-1242. [There is also a series of numbers:] 3.50, 4.10, 5.30, 6.20.
  - Hotel Aldolphus, Dallas, Texas, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_893; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a drawing of a large hotel in a city. Caption on front: Hotel Adolphus Dallas, Texas. Caption on verso: 825 rooms with bath, 300 fully air-conditioned. Rates from $2.50 per day. Home of the popular Century Room. H. Fuller Stevens Managing Director.
  - Galveston, The Treasure Island, “Playground of Texas”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_894; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a drawing of seven planes flying over the shore of a large city with a couple piers in the water. Caption on front: Galveston, The Treasure Island, "Playground of Texas."
  - In the Surf along the Beach Front, Galveston, Texas, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_895; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a drawing of a beach near a city scape. There are people playing in the water and on the beach. Caption on front: In the Surf along the Beach Front, Galveston, Texas.
  - Pioneer Life in Honey Lake Valley, Cal., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_896; Postcard; 5 1/2 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a pioneer standing next to a covered wagon without the canvas covering. Captions on front: Pioneer life in honey lake valley, Cal.; Chuck Wagon and Cook.
  - Mission San Rafael Arcangel, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_897; Postcard; 5 x 3 1/4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a sepia tinted drawing of a single story building with a hill in the background. Captions on front: Geo. D. Shearer & Co. Real Estate Agents Opp. Union Depot San Rafael, Cal.; 1491 - Mission San Rafael Arcangel, founded 1817, San Rafael, California.
    There are two copies of this postcard. Copy 1 - Handwritten on verso: 226 $20.00.
  - On the shore at Liberty Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_898; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of some people fishing and sitting by the shore of a lake. In the foreground is a pitched tent. Caption on front: On the shore at Liberty Lake. Caption on verso: Nature has provided an ideal place at Liberty Lake for family outings, picnics and summer camps. Frequent trains to the lake via Coeur d'Alene electric line.
  - Liberty Lake – Spokane’s bathing resort, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_899; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of recreational activities on a lake shore. Some people are swimming and others are preparing a row boat. Caption on front: Liberty Lake - Spokane's bathing resort. Caption on verso: Of easy access, via electric line, Liberty Lake is a delightful place for family and school picnics. Boating, bathing and fishing.
  - Beautiful Hayden Lake, Idaho, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_900; Postcard; 6 7/8 x 5 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of cabins on top of a ridge overlooking a lake. Ther are a couple boats on the lake. Caption on front: Beautiful Hayden Lake, Idaho. Caption on verso: Summer cottages among the pines at Haden Lake can be rented for family use. Apply at the hotel on the grounds or Terminal Bldg. Spokanes. Special commutation rates for summer residents via Coeur d'Alene electric line from Spokane.
  - Beautiful Hayden Lake, Idaho, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_901; Postcard; 7 x 5 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a view looking over a lake with coniferous trees around the edges. Caption on front: Beautiful Haden Lake, Idaho. Caption on verso: Hayden Lake, a Washington and Idaho resort east of Spokane, is reached by the Coeur d'Alene electric line. Golf, tennis, boating, bathing and excellent trout fishing.
  - Factories of the Firestone Tire & Rubber oc., Akron, O., U.S.A., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_902; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a drawing of a large four story building with a smoke stack. There is another inset image of another large factory building labeled "Rim Plant." Captions of this front: Factories of the Firestone Tire & Rubber Co., Akron, O., U.S.A.; New plant - Largest tire building in the world.
  - Balanced Rock, Sherman Hill, Wyoming, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_903; Postcard; 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a stack of rocks. There are some dead tree trunks around the pile. Caption on front: Balanced Rock, Sherman Hill, Wyoming.
  - Mining buildings, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_904; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of mining buildings. There are two snow covered roads diverging from where the photo was taken.
  - Crater Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_905; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Photograph of Crater Lake. Caption on verso: Crater Lake Discovered by John Wesley Hillman in 1853, this beautiful lake has since come to be known as one of the outstanding wonders of scenic beauty.
    Was stored in a yellow folding envelope with the caption on the front: Mike Roberts Crater Lake in Color, 6 views, Reproduced from Kodachromes/color productions. Photograph has been resleeved and rehoused.
  - Lodge at Crater Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_906; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 6)
    Photograph of a large three story lodge. Caption on verso: Crater Lake - The Lodge, Located on the rim of beautiful Crater Lake, the Lodge is a luxurious and comfortable resting place for travelers.
  - Wizard Island, Crater Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_907; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 6)
    Photograph of a view of Crater Lake with a boy in a yllow shirt and blue background in the foreground. Caption on verso: Wizard Island from Lookout Point, Composed of cinders, Wizard Island rises nearly 800 feet above the rich blue of Crater Lake. Within its cone is a 90-ft crater whose circumference is over a thousand feet.
  - The Phantom Ship, Crater Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_908; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/4 (Box 6)
    Photograph of a large island in a lake. There is a boat in the foreground. Caption on front: The Phantom Ship, Crater Lake National Park, Towering more than 165 feet above Crater Lake's blue, the Phantom Ship, formed by the volcano whose erruption created the Lake, serenely withstands the centuries.
  - Crater Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_909; Photographic Print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 6)
    Photograph of Crater Lake. Caption on verso: Crater Lake Within Wizard Island is a deep volcanic crater more than 1000 feet in circumference. Towering vari-colored cliffs contrast with the deep blue of the Lake.
  - Crater Lake, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_910; Photographic Print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 6)
    Photograph of Crater Lake with Wizard Island in the middle ground and a coniferous tree in the foreground. Caption on verso: Crater Lake, Its almost freezing water, harboring rainbow trout and silverside salmon, Crater Lake's dramatic blue contrasts with the multicolored cliffs which surround it.
  - Souvenir of Excelsior Springs, Mo., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_911; Photographic prints; 6 1/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Group of photographs. On the front of the envelope is written: Seeing Excelsior Springs, MO. The Great Health Resort of the Year. On the back of the envelope: Souvenir of Excelsior Springs, Mo. Addressed to: Miss Helen Howard, Cambridge, Webr. Photographs are double sided and attached to each other. Partial list of titles of photographs: Elms Hotel, Fire-Proof; Hotel Royal; The Snapps Hotel; Hotel Plaza; Omaha House and Salt Sea Springs; View of Sulpho Saline and Siloam Springs and Excelsior Hotel; Crystal Lithia Springs; LIthiated Soda Spring, Excelsior Spring, MO.
    Stored in one brown envelope. Full list of titles: Elms Hotel, Fire-Proof; Hotel Royal; The Snapps Hotel; Hotel Plaza; Omaha House and Salt Sea Springs; View of Sulpho Saline and Siloam Springs and Excelsior Hotel; Crystal Lithia Springs; LIthiated Soda Spring, Excelsior Spring, MO.; Sanford House, Excelsior Spring, MO.; Hotel Nebraska, Corner of Main and South Streets; Avalon Apartments; The Pickwick Apartments; Anderson Flats and Cottage; Siloam Springs; Lithia No. 1, Excelsior Springs, MO.; Regent Spring, Excelsior Springs, MO.; Natrona Soda Spring, Excelsior Springs, MO.; Siloam Bath House; Salt Sulphur Bath House; Golf Links looking Toward Club House; Night Scene, Marietta Street, Excelsior Springs, MO.; Salt Sulphur Spring, Excelsior Springs, MO.
  - Lion Hotel Shrewsbury, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_912; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a drawing of a city street. Caption on front: Lion Hotel Shrewsbury. Caption on verso: The Lion at Shrewsbury, was the house of the famous Lawrence who procured the opening of the Holyhead road. It was visited by Dickens and by De Quincey.
  - Old Fire Place, Shrewsbury Castle, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_913; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard of a photograph of an empty room with a large fireplace in the wall. Caption on front: Old fire place, Shrewsbury Castle.
  - Wyle Cop, Shrewsbury, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_914; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a busy city street with townhouses on both sides. Caption on front: Wyle Cop, Shewsbury.
    Same image negative used as for photograph 00915.
  - Wyle Cop, Shrewsbury, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_915; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Postcard from a photograph of a busy city street with townshouses on both sides. Caption on front: Wyle Cop, Shrewsbury.
    Same image negative used as for photograph 00914.
  - The British convict ship “Success”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_916; Postcard; 3 3/8 x 5 1/4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a man sitting in a room. His writs are chained to the wall. Captions on front: The British Convict Ship "Success" oldest ship afloat launched at Moulmein, Burmah 1790; The dreaded black hole where hundreds died.
  - Group of people standing around a fountain, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_917; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Handcolored postcard of a group of people standing around a fountain. Caption on front: Bad Orb. Inneres der Phillips-Quelle.
  - Bull Fighters, Tia Juana, Mexico, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_918; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 4, Folder 2)